yoo.ge 2012-10-15

# Privacy Policy - - Games at Yoo.ge - Play Online Games

Collection and Use of Personal Information: When we use the term "Personal Information" we mean information such as your first/middle initial or name and last name, street address, town or city, state, zip code, telephone number, instant-messenger nickname, blog or other personal website URL, date of birth, e-mail address and any other information that would allow someone to identify you or contact you. Personal Information also includes information such as lists of your friends' real names and their email addresses, instant-messenger nicknames or other personal identifiable information that you may add to such friend lists and your transactions or relationship with us, if you have been a user of the Site. We collect Personal Information about you when you visit the Site and input information, whether you are registering to use any features or functions of the Site, participating in Promotions (as defined in the Terms of Use Agreement, or in the course of any other exchanges of information, transactions and activities. We may use the information we obtain from you, including Personal Information, to tailor your experience of the Site, to display content we think may be of interest to you, or to let us customize what you see when you visit or use the Site according to your preferences. 

**Cookie**  
We store catgeory names in your browser to offer games you playing most. 

**Non-personal information**  
Non-personal information is information that cannot identify you personally, such as: (i) the IP address of the computer you are using);. This Web site uses cookies to collect non-personal information about our users. A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser's files for our reference. Cookies allow our server computer to recognize you when you return to this Web site and retain any preferences you may have provided. If you do not wish to receive cookies, consult your browser's help menu in order to configure your browser so that it will alert you when a cookie is about to be sent to your computer and provide you with a choice of whether or not to accept it. We may use non-personal information to calculate overall usage statistics and to better understand our visitors, but not to track any individual user. 

**Personal information**  
Personal information refers to information specifically about a particular user, such as: (i) name; (ii) age; (iii) address; (iv) email address; and (v) telephone number. Personal information will only be collected by fair and lawful means. The only personal information we will collect and retain is the personal information voluntarily provided by you when you: (i) register as a member on our websites; (ii) submit answers to surveys or questionnaires; or (iii) contact us with questions or comments about this Web site. We may use your personal information to: (i) provide information or services you requested; (ii) send you information about products, information or services that may be of interest to you (email communications will always provide you with an "unsubscribe" option); and (iii) generate statistics and aggregate reports for our internal use, such as the development of our services. 

**No disclosure of personal information to third parties**  
We are not distributing your personal information to third parties. 

\------  
updated: January 09, 2011
